yovia.com 2014-02-28

# Yovia - Privacy Policy

This is the web site of Yovia LLC.

Our postal address is:   
1372 Beach Blvd  
Jacksonville Beach, Fl 32250   

We can be reached via e-mail at  info@yovia.com, or you can reach us by telephone at 904-242-2669. 

_How We Collect Information_

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, as well as information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information, Facebook or Twitter account information and/or site registrations. If you give us your email address or other data because you want to be a Yovia Contributor, because you want to start a social velocity campaign, are responding to an offer or giveaway, or because you want more information about Yovia, we will obviously take the data you provide and keep it handy for working with you. 

We also use Google Analytics, which records information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. Google Analytics anonymously tracks how visitors interact with a website, including where they came from and what they did on a site. If you visit our site and click on the widget on the main page, Google Analytics will make note of that, and it could also make note of your Internet Protocol (IP) address and any other information your browser sends. It does not, however, collect information such as your name, address, financial information, or any other personal data. That information must be provided with your consent and is never gathered without your knowledge. 

_How Information Is Used_

The information we collect is used to provide requested services, improve the content of our Web page, and notify you about updates to our Web site. It could also be shared with agents or contractors who assist in providing support for our internal operations, disclosed when legally required to do so (at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Website and applicable laws or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Website), and disclosed to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, sale of assets or other corporate change respecting the website, should something like that ever happen. 

If you supply us with your email address, connect your Yovia account to a social network, provide postal address or phone number online you will receive only the communications for which you provided us your information. We don’t use your info for other purposes without your consent, and we don’t sell or share your info with third parties, unless you have specifically requested to receive more information.

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail, writing us, or calling us at the above address. You may also opt-out of any Yovia Newsletters via a link provided in each email. 

From time to time, we may make changes to our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our website to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of any new uses of your information. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our website periodically. 

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to all information (including proprietary information) that we maintain about them. After all, it’s YOUR information. Consumers can access this information by e-mail us at the above address or writing to us at the above address. We also offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information, financial information, and other unique identifiers, again by contacting us at the above address, email address or phone number and letting us know what information needs to be changed. 

With respect to security: We utilize best-practices to put security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. We restrict access to personal information to Yovia employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. 

This Privacy Policy applies only to those websites owned and maintained by Yovia. Any third party sites linked to or from Yovia websites are not covered by this policy. 

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number and we’ll do our best to address your concerns.
